Hello everyone, welcome back to to this another new tutorial topic. So today I can going to show you the MongoDB and
most using the table information with the MongoDB shell. Okay, so in this session for quick
explore for how to update for the MongoDB documents using for the various update operations and
settings. Okay, so I hope I have perfectly collecting the MongoDB shell for my code editors. Okay,
So now just choose for the MongoDB shell and my hair the data is okay. So you can see here
and now just I can go for the first example, first of all, you're using for the setup part. Okay,
so now here first of all, I can just go here and type for here simply db dot the
the students for the collections name used for the dot and type for here. This is the
this type the update one. Okay, and now here cutin the fence is also cutin for the curly brackets.
So different for the name. So name is
Johan. Okay, so now here I can simply type the Johan and here cutin the format and use for the
curly brackets and in this inside first of all the dollar sign and the set function now here
I can use for that again the curly brackets and then type for the each column. So it is unified.
Okay, so here simply created for this collection. So now here I have completely
based into and you can see here this knowledge is two and here you can see the the MongoDB
acknowledge successful updated the document. Okay, so now here going to be perfectly next
step here is for another using for the dollar sign for answer to just remove the next door. Okay,
so now here I can just go for and just type copy and here I can just type for the db dot
use the just use the collection and here just type for dot is called the update one. Okay,
and now here I can go into define the curly brackets. So it is for the name field. So now the name field
used for the name is. Okay, and also here I can use for I can create this comma and type for
again the curly brackets. So in this inside I can use for the dollar sign and perfectly type the
unsafe. Okay, so now here the sample data now here I can just use for the see this and type for
here the status. Okay, and in clear and we have simply clear the double quotation. So here this is
the command is removed from the service field document in the collections where the name field is
placed. Okay, now here perfectly defined the interface and you can see here the second knowledge
is perfectly operating. Okay, so now here is for another example. So now here I create for
increment operator. So now just run the same process the db then students is perfectly
typed for the students and now here again it is the update one function script. Okay,
now I can create here this format. So define for here I'll take the name. So now I can use
for the name is this. Okay, and create for the format and use for again the curly brackets then
use the INC for the increment. Then I can create for. So it is not the double quotation is
simply create for here the curly brackets and join inside the type is code. Okay, so this code is
this. Okay, so now here perfectly at this command increment the whole view of the document in the
collection where the name field is more better. Okay, so now here this complete and press for
the enter and you can see this command is perfectly working. So here you can acknowledge the two
inside the ID. Now this matches the counter and modify one and the absurd one. So here this is perfectly
working and next use the MongoDB acknowledgement successfully implemented for the numeric page. Okay,
so you can see here perfectly created in this statement and here I have perfectly used for the
three options. You can choose here and you can use another option to create new first of all I can
type for the DB. Okay, so DB dot. Students dot used perfectly this the update one. Okay, and create
for the parentheses and also create the curly brackets. So here I can define the name. So the name is
used for this. Okay, and now I can create for use for here again the the curly brackets and in
this inside use for the push method. And now page here I'll just use the one and here I can
just type for the copies. Okay, so I can just perfectly type the copies in the double quotation and
you can see that you can see the perfectly defined now I can just use the enter and you can see here
perfectly working and now this acknowledgement is good. Okay, so this is completely done into
recision and I hope you've got it now so thank you for what's new and happy coding.